schedulesource.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy | ScheduleSource

ScheduleSource is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals who visit our websites or register to use our services. This Privacy Statement covers the information practices of both our commercial websites including www.schedulesource.com and private websites from which we deliver the ScheduleSource TeamWork Suite of Products and Services. ScheduleSource’s websites may contain links to other websites. The information practices or the content of such other websites is governed by the privacy statements of such other websites.

**1\. Information collected:**

When soliciting information about our services or registering to use the services, we require you to provide us with personal contact information, such as name, company name, address, phone number, and email address (“Required Contact Information”). When purchasing the services, we may require you to provide us with financial and billing information, such as billing name and address, credit card number and related information (“Billing Information”). We use credit card information solely to check financial qualifications and collect payment from customers.

As you navigate our websites, ScheduleSource may also collect information through the use of commonly used information-gathering tools such as cookies. Navigational Information includes standard information from your web browser (such as browser type and browser language), your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, and actions on your subscribed websites such as logins, transaction history and other audit information that is a collected as an inherent feature of the ScheduleSource TeamWork product.

**2\. Using the Information Collected:**

We use data received from prospects and customers to perform the services you request. For example, if you fill out a “Contact Me” web form, we will use the information provided to contact you about your interest in the Services. We may use information you provide to contact you to further discuss your interest in the Services and to send you information about our offerings.

Data entered by you or by us on your behalf into the TeamWork Product is never shared and is never accessed except when required to provide technical support to your users.

**3\. Web Site Information**

**Cookies:**  ScheduleSource uses cookies to make interactions with our websites easy and meaningful. When you visit one of our websites, ScheduleSource’s servers send a cookie to your computer. Standing alone, cookies do not personally identify you; they merely recognize your Web browser. Unless you choose to identify yourself to ScheduleSource, either by responding to a promotional offer, opening an account, or filling out a web form, you remain anonymous to us.

ScheduleSource uses cookies that are session-based and persistent-based. Session cookies exist only during one session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser software or turn off your computer. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you close your browser or turn off your computer. Please note that if you disable your Web browser’s ability to accept cookies, you will be able to navigate our commercial websites but you will not be able to successfully use the TeamWork product.

**IP Addresses:**  When you use ScheduleSource’s websites, we collect your Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses to track and aggregate non-personal information. ScheduleSource also collects IP addresses from Customers when they log into the Services as part of our “Identity Confirmation” and “IP Range Restrictions” security features.

**Social Media:**  Our Web sites may use social media features. These features may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media Features are hosted by a third party. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the entity providing them.

**Public forums:**  ScheduleSource may provide bulletin boards or blogs on our websites. Any information you choose to submit in such a forum may be read, collected, or used by others who visit these forums and may be used to send you unsolicited messages. ScheduleSource is not responsible for personal information you choose to submit in these forums.

**Customer Testimonials:**  ScheduleSource posts a list of Customers on our website that contains information such as Customer names. ScheduleSource obtains the consent of each Customer prior to posting any information on such a list or posting testimonials.

**Sharing of Information Collected:**  ScheduleSource does not share information collected on its commercial websites or in its TeamWork application except when providing integrated services that exchange data with your authorized systems. ScheduleSource does not share, sell, rent, or trade any information with third parties for their promotional purposes.

**Business Partners:**  From time to time, ScheduleSource may partner with other companies to jointly offer products or services. Those joint products or services may exchange data, including your data as entered into the joint product.

**Third Parties:**  ScheduleSource does not authorize the collection of personal information by third parties through advertising technologies deployed on our Web sites, nor do we share personal information with any third parties collected from our Web sites.

**Billing:**  ScheduleSource may use a third-party service provider to manage credit card processing. This service provider is not permitted to store, retain, or use Billing Information except for the sole purpose of credit card processing on our behalf.

**Compelled Disclosure:**  ScheduleSource reserves the right to use or disclose information provided if required by law or if we reasonably believe that use or disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.

**International transfer of information collected:**  We primarily store data about our Customers and Customer entered Data in the United States. We transfer and access such information from around the world. This Privacy Statement shall apply even if ScheduleSource transfers Data about ScheduleSource Customers to other countries.

**Customer Data:**  ScheduleSource Customers enter data into our TeamWork for their use. ScheduleSource will not review, share, distribute, or reference any such Customer Data except as provided in the ScheduleSource Master Subscription Agreement, or as may be required by law. ScheduleSource may access Customer Data only for the purpose of providing the Services or preventing or addressing service or technical problems or as may be required by law.

**4\. Security:**  ScheduleSource uses robust, continuously monitored security measures to protect data About ScheduleSource Customers and data entered by our Customers.

**5\. Changes:**  ScheduleSource reserves the right to change this Privacy Statement. ScheduleSource will provide notification of the material changes to this Privacy Statement through our websites prior to the change taking effect.

**6\. Contacting us:**  Questions regarding this Privacy Statement or the information practices of our Web sites should be directed to [support@schedulesource.com](mailto:support@schedulesource.com).
